<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Temecula Real Estate Podcast with Josh Painter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Impact Real Estate - your professional Temecula Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Josh Painter</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-04-07 14:02:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Josh Painter</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Temecula, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>jpainter78@gmail.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Josh Painter</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Josh Painter</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Temecula, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Temecula Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Impact Real Estate - your professional Temecula Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Coronavirus Addendum/Amendment - California Association of Realtors Form CVA 3/20</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/coronavirus-addendumamendment-california-association-of-realtors-form-cva-320.html</link>
        
        <author>Josh Painter</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-26 16:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

The coronavirus addendum issued by the California Association of Realtors is not mandatory, but you’re able to include it anytime you’re writing an offer. If you’re a seller, and the buyer did not include it, you’re able to counter their offer by including it. 

If you’re already in a transaction, however, neither party is required to sign it; if you send it over and the other party refuses to sign, there’s really no recourse for you—hopefully, the parties are reasonable and willing to work out the best route. 

Every once in a while, life brings you those “Oh sh*t” moments—that’s the reason for this document. Some hypothetical, yet entirely plausible, ways COVID-19 could disrupt a transaction include lender and title company offices shutting down, a loss of employment, and travel bans prohibiting parties from signing documents. This preemptive addendum allows a buyer and seller to come to an agreement before any of that stuff happens. 

Essentially, it’s a way for parties to say, “Hey, I don’t know if any of these scenarios will transpire, but if they do, these are our options.”

“Every once in a while, life brings you those “Oh sh*t” moments—that’s the reason for this document.”

Here’s what the addendum allows: 


  Buyer and seller can agree to postpone the close of escrow up to 30 days to accommodate unforeseen circumstances. 
  If a loan contingency has already been removed, but due to unforeseen circumstances, the buyer may be now unable to fund the loan, escrow can be canceled and the deposit returned to the buyer. 
  Mutual agreement to cancel simply due to the general circumstances of the COVID-19 outbreak. 


If you have more specific questions on this or any other real estate topic, please feel free to reach out to me by phone or email. I’m happy to help you out and address your concerns. 


  

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’ve been getting a flood of questions about the new coronavirus addendum issued by the California Association of Realtors, so here’s what you need to know about it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Josh Painter</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’ve been getting a flood of questions about the new coronavirus addendum issued by the California Association of Realtors, so here’s what you need to know about it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Temecula, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Josh Painter</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Josh Painter</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Impact Real Estate - your professional Temecula Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
